No Man of God is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Amber Sealey.
The complicated relationship that formed between the FBI analyst Bill Hagmaier and
serial killer Ted Bundy during Bundy's final years on death row.
Bill Hagmaier, played by Elijah Wood.
Ted Bundy, played by Luke Kirby.
Carolyn Lieberman, played by Aleksa Palladino.
Roger Depue, played by Robert Patrick.
Warden Wilkenson, played by W. Earl Brown.
Assistant Warden Paul Decker, played by Gilbert Owuor.
Man of God (Greek: Ο Άνθρωπος του Θεού) is a 2021 English-language Greek biographical drama film written and directed by Yelena
Popovic, and starring Aris Servetalis as Nectarios of Aegina and also starring Mickey Rourke and Alexander Petrov.
The film explores themes of prison, florida, confession, fbi, death row.
The tone is emotional and intense.